A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 2008-2018 (bulk 2014-2018)
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Public Relations, 2010-2018., Extent: 12 boxes (4.1 cu. ft.). (Box 29-40)
  - K & O Distillers Opening, 2015 January 29 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Sec. Warner, Cuba Briefing, 2015 January 30 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - NASA Wallops Center, 2015 February 4 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Eastern Shore Ag Trade Conference, 2015 February 10 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - VALOR Program, 2015 February 12 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - University of Richmond, Spiders in Law and Public Policy, 2015 February 23 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Governor's Cup Gala, 2015 February 24 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Board of Forestry Meeting, 2015 February 24 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Cirrus Vodka Tour, 2015 February 25 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - LUMI Juices Meeting, 2015 February 26 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - VNRLI [Virginia Natural Resources Leadership Institute], 2015 March 4 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University eMBA Program, 2015 March 6 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - USDA Agribusiness Mission to South East Asia, 2015 March 14-15 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Farm to School Conference, 2015 March 18 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Universal Leaf, 2015 March 25 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Rural Center, 2015 March 31 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - VSU 125th Celebration, 2015 March-July (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - NASA Develop, 2015 April 17 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Barboursville Historic Marker, 2015 April 17 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - VNLA [Virginia Nursery & Landscape Association] Tree Ceremony, 2015 April 20 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Agriculture Secretaries Meeting, 2015 April 22 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Southern Plant Board Meeting, 2015 April 27 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Eastern Wheat & Southern Small Grain Workers Conference, 2015 April 28-30 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Wine Education Summit, 2015 April 29 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - WTNA Conference, 2015 May 12 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - VMA [Virginia Maritime Association] Annual Dinner, 2015 May 14 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - TMA Conference, 2015 May 19 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Cargill Safety Recognition Event, 2015 May 20 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - VSWCB [Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Board] Meeting, 2015 May 20 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Tobacco Commission, 2015 May 20-21 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Sabre Chick Pea Meeting, 2015 May 26 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - State Department, Ambassador visit, 2015 May 28 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Poultry Industry letter, 2015 May (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Pittsylvania County Poultry Tour, 2015 June 3 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - VDACS International Trade Rep Meeting, 2015 June 23 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Hops in the Park, 2015 June 23 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Boys State of Virginia, 2015 June 25 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Hardywood Brewery, 2015 June 29 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Gracie Goodpasture Meeting, 2015 June 29 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - VFA Tour, 2015 June 30 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Poultry Industry, 2015 June (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Tyson Foods, Inc., 2015 July 7 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Peck Marine Terminal, 2015 July 8 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Latvian Ambassador, 2015 July 8 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Rappahannock Broadband Forum, 2015 July 8 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - High School Leadership Group, 2015 July 10 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Broadband Advisory Council, 2015 July 13 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - VPGC [Virginia Poultry Growers Cooperative, Inc.] Annual meeting, 2015 July 16 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Dairy Center grand opening, 2015 July 17 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Governor's Agriculture Day in the Valley, 2015 July 22 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Shenandoah Valley Partnership Annual meeting, 2015 July 22 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Food System Council, 2015 July 31 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Buddhist Television Network, 2015 August 10 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - VAC Roundtable Valley, 2015 August 13 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Rural Center Panel (Staunton, Va.), 2015 August 17 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Rockingham County Fair, 2015 August 19 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Miller Coors Luncheon, 2015 August 19 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Ardent InstaMeet, 2015 August 19 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Gleaning Day, 2015 August 20 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Leaf Tobacco Summit, 2015 August 20 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - First Lady Red Wine testing, 2019 August 24 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Eastern Shore Biz Association, 2015 August 25 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Ambassador Miguel Ntutumu Evuna Andeme [Republic of Equatorial Guinea], 2015 August 27 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Craft Beer Day, 2015 August 27 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - VLVA [Virginia Loggers Association] Annual meeting, 2015 August 29 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Tyton BioEnergy Systems, 2015 September 10 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - VFPA meeting, 2015 September 12 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - New River Valley, Planning for Ag in SWVA, 2015 September 21 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - University of Richmond, Globalization lecture, 2015 September 25 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Maryland-Virginia Agriculture Marketing & Development Professionals, Tour of Southern Virginia, 2015 September 29-October 2 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - State Fair of Virginia, 2015 September 30 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - 4-H Ag Commodities Tour, 2015 October 5 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Red Rocker Candy, 2015 October 14 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Hunan Tobacco, 2015 October 16 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - October Virginia Wine Month, 2015 October 20 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Agri-Women Kick-Off, 2015 October 20 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - NCGA [National Corn Growers Association] State and National Execs meeting, 2015 October 22 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Urban Ag Summit, 2015 October 23 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Green Plains, 2015 October 26 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Order of Merit and Monteith Trophy Reception for Luca Paschina, 2015 October 26 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Soil to Glass, 2015 October 27 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Healthy Food Retail Summit, 2015 October 28 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Omega Protein Corp. Site Visit, 2015 October (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - American Wine Society Conference, 2015 November 6 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Montpelier Hunt Races, 2015 November 7 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Business Leader's Dinner, 2015 November 9 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Distilling Company, 2015 November 10 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Williamsburg Harvest Celebration, 2015 November 11-15 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Cuba Trade Mission Discussion, 2015 November 12 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Christmas Tree Delivery, 2015 November 30 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation Annual Convention, 2015 December 2 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - VSWCD Annual meeting, 2015 December 7 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Rappahannock Oyster Cruise, 2015 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Cabinet Retreat, 2016 January 4-5 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Worker misclassification meeting, 2016 January 6 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Certified Work Ready Committee, 2016 January 12 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Mobilitie, 2016 January 12 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Palo Alto Networks call, 2016 January 12 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - NNPDC [Northern Neck Planning District Commission] Quarterly meeting, 2016 January 25 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Food and Beverage Expo, 2016 March 2 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Ambassador German Hugo Rojas Irigoyen [Paraguay], 2016 March 22 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation meeting, 2016 May 24 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Ambassador Juan Carlos Pinzon [Colombia], 2016 May 25 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Distillers Association meeting, 2016 June 10 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Budget Rollout press events, 2016 June 13-17 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Alcoa and Performance Livestock and Feed, 2016 June 14 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Virginia State Park visit, 2016 June 15 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Agency Executive agreements, 2016 June 23 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Project 950, 2016 July 25 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - VAPDC [Virginia Association of Planning District Commissions] Annual Conference, 2016 July 27 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Mega Sites, 2016 July 28 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Fountainhead Properties, 2016 August 1 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - International Budget Rollout, 2016 August 2 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - RePower South, 2016 August 3 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Rotary Club of the James River, 2016 August 24 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 2016 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Agricultural and Forestry exports, 2016 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Invitations, 2016-2017 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 2017-2018 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Rural Caucus meeting, 2017 February 8 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Mexico Marketing Mission, 2017 May 1-4 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - NY-Dallas Marketing Mission, 2017 May 9-11 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Wine Board, 2017 August 16 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - VEDP Committee on International Trade, 2017 November 2 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Another Chance to Excel, 2017 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Decision briefs, 2017 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Farm Winery Study, 2017 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Farm Winery Study, 2017 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Project plans and events, 2017 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Rural Rehabilitation Trust Fund, Grant applications, 2017-2018 (Box 40, Folder 3)